DispatchAI – AI Operations Agent for Chauffeur Booking
Demo Mode – Deterministic AI workflow for reliable demonstrations
Customer submits a booking request
AI analyzes the natural-language message
AI extracts structured booking information
Address validation using demo data
Booking draft created
Dispatcher reviews the booking
Status: Pending Approval
Human approval completes the booking
Live Mode – OpenAI, OneMap, and Supabase
Processing a real booking request
GPT-5.6 extracts booking details
OneMap validates Singapore addresses
Booking saved to Supabase
Dispatcher reviews the live booking
Booking approved and ready for operations
DispatchAI combines AI reasoning with trusted external services while keeping humans in control.